PureVPN’s Privacy Policy
========================

We do NOT keep any logs that can identify or help in monitoring a user’s activity.

Introduction
------------

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors and service users. In this policy, “we”, “us” and “our” refer to PureVPN.

Collected information
---------------------

When you sign up with PureVPN, we only ask for the following information:

* Name.
* Email address.
* Password.
* Payment method.

This information is collected and stored to provide and improve our services to you (“stored data”). No other information is collected or stored at signup.

Additionally, we also collect the following information for customer support and service excellence reasons during service usage:

* Day of connection – We **do NOT** track or store the time you connected to our services.
* ISP Tracking – We **do NOT** track or store your personal IP or exact location.
* Connection time – We **do NOT** track or store the specific times you connected to our server.
* Usage and Activity logs – We **do NOT** monitor or store any activity log for any user.

For app and service improvements we collect the following information:

* Software analytics and statistics.
* Data from emails, live chats, and feedback forms.

None of the data listed above can be used to identify or track users.

‘However, we do NOT store any logs that can identify or help in monitoring your activity. We do this to ensure PureVPN has no information to share even if we are forced to. None of the following records are stored by PureVPN’.

* Browsing activity.
* Identifiable connection logs.
* Records of IPs assigned.
* A customer’s original IP.
* Connection timestamps.
* Browsing history.
* Sites visited.
* Outgoing traffic.
* Content or data accessed.
* DNS queries generated by the user.

#### You are invisible – even we can’t see what you do online

Our systems, processes and servers are designed not to store any of the above mentioned user information . We do this by design to ensure no data can be stored.

Use of stored data
------------------

The information we collected enables us to provide our services to you. We process the information for the following:

* To provide, operate, and maintain our services.
* To improve, personalize and expand our services.
* To analyze and improve user experience.
* To communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners. We communicate with our users for user service, providing updates and other information related to the services, and for marketing and promotional purposes.
* To process your transactions.
* To improve our contract management.
* To enforce our Terms of Service or other legal rights.

#### Our VPN connection logs DO NOT collect:

Your origin IP

Your VPN IP

The specific time a user connected to our server

Any activity conducted when connected to our servers

**NOTE:** In the case of a Dedicated IP addon purchase, a fixed and dedicated VPN IP is assigned to the user which remains in our records for 25 days after a subscription ends.

#### Bandwidth use and consumption

All PureVPN subscribers get access to unlimited bandwidth, irrespective of how it is used. We keep track of the total bandwidth consumed by a user to make sure everybody is getting the highest speeds and the best possible experience from our product.

PureVPN reserves the right to contact users about bandwidth irregularities and service disruption for other users resulting from these irregularities.

#### Software analytics and statistics

PureVPN collects minimal connection statistics and reports. None of these include identifiable data or behavior, such as web traffic details, IP addresses and DNS requests.

This collection is done strictly to ensure the best possible service and customer support is delivered to our customers.

PureVPN conducts VPN diagnostics and monitors crash reports to:

* Better understand the functionality of our software.
* See how often the PureVPN app is used.
* Understand events occurring within the app.
* See aggregated usage.
* Track performance data.
* Track failed connection attempts.

We use a number of tools in our client software for the reporting mentioned above. These tools are:

* Google Analytics – Please visit Google’s Terms [here.](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/)
* Tunes – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/)
* Firebase – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy)
* New Relic – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy)
* MixPanel – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* Facebook Pixel – Please visit Facebook’s Privacy Policy [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). You can stop the use of your data for the purpose of displaying Facebook ads by clicking [here.](https://www.facebook.com/adpreferences/ad_settings/?entry_product=account_settings_menu)
* Intercom.io – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy)
* Sentry – Please visit the Privacy Policy [here.](https://sentry.io/privacy/)

It is the responsibility of our customers to keep their apps updated at all times to ensure compatibility with our terms and conditions\***\*Users are notified about upgrades whenever possible.**

#### Data from emails, live chats, and feedback forms

Other than users’ data, it is important for PureVPN to keep a record of all user correspondence to ensure smooth service delivery and superior customer service. We keep a record of all correspondence, be it questions, complaints or compliments submitted via our apps, website or extensions.

PureVPN uses multiple third-party platforms for customer support and correspondence:

* Zendesk: for support tickets (read their privacy policy [here](https://www.zendesk.com/company/agreements-and-terms/privacy-policy//)).
* Intercom: for customer support via chat (read their privacy policy [here](https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy)).
* Mailchimp: for emails (read their privacy policy [here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)).
* SendGrid: for emails (read their privacy policy [here](https://api.sendgrid.com/privacy.html)).
* MixPanel: to maintain relations with our users (read their privacy policy [here](https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/)).

The customer’s name and email address are stored with the third-party platform when they correspond with PureVPN while using any of these services.

#### International data transfers

Our systems are spread across the globe, which means the stored data is traveling through servers in multiple locations which might or might not be in the customer’s country of residence. While we rely on some third-party service providers to deliver our services, we make sure that the stored data is protected during this process. PureVPN has strict data protection agreements in place with all providers.

It is important for users to understand that their stored data will be transferred and/or processed when required, as it is an integral part to maintain excellence in our services and live up to our Terms of Service.

Security of collected information
---------------------------------

With the exception to the stored data mentioned in section 2, PureVPN neither stores any user data nor shares, sells or rents it out to any third party. Hence no such information is kept with us. The only information mentioned in section 2 is stored to provide the products and services required by users which is kept safe without sharing or selling it to any third party.

#### Security measures to protect your information

All stored data is secured with strong cryptographic algorithms wherever required.

PureVPN takes appropriate measures for the protection of all customer information against unauthorized access, alteration, destruction and disclosure of data. Access to personal customer information by PureVPN employees, contractors and agents is restricted.

It is important for all users to understand that despite the strictest precautionary measures taken, no system can be declared 100% foolproof, protected or secure.

#### Data retention policy and your data protection rights

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have the following data protection rights:

* You can always access, correct and update the information you provided to us, within your member’s area profile.
* You can also exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send to you.
* You may also request deletion of your personal user profile, if you decide to leave our services completely. You can do so at any time by sending an email at support@purevpn.com. If you request the deletion of your profile, it may take up to a month (30 days) to complete. Your email address will be kept and used to avoid account duplication and creation of fake accounts in your name. Your email address will be deleted only after we receive an explicit request from you to do so.

#### Cookies and PureVPN

PureVPN utilizes different types of cookies to store information related to a visitor on our website. This is done in order to provide the best experience, and to deliver advertising messages and offers that are relevant to our users.

Please see How [PureVPN Uses Cookies](https://www.purevpn.com/cookies) to get a better understanding about the cookies we employ, what type of data is collected, how that data is used, and how a user can opt-out of this program.

#### What data does PureAI share with OpenAI? How is it being used by OpenAI?

The prompts you submit to PureAI will be shared with OpenAI. For example, if you ask PureAI ‘what is VPN’, the text in quotes will be shared with OpenAI. OpenAI will not use your prompts to train or improve their models. OpenAI will use your prompts for content moderation purposes and will delete those prompts after 30 days. You can learn more about how OpenAI uses your prompts by reviewing OpenAI’s API Data Usage Policy .You will remain completely anonymous while using the PureAI. Your personally identifiable information will never be shared with OpenAI to ensure you remain anonymous while using the PureAI.

#### What data is being shared with third parties when I use PureAI?

Your prompts (e.g., when you ask PureAI to ‘what is VPN’) will be shared with OpenAI. However, your prompts and customer data associated with your PureVPN account will never be shared with any other third parties. Your prompts and queries will be stored by PureAI but will never be attributable to you as a user. This data is only collected to ensure the services we offer to our users are up to the mark.

Third-party website links
-------------------------

PureVPN’s website might contain links to other third-party websites. We do not control how they operate their privacy practices nor can we take responsibility for them.

Financial and credit information
--------------------------------

As with all online businesses, PureVPN also uses third-party payment processors. All payment data rests with the respective processor.

However, some do require us to process the payment. And in such cases we process all payments realtime and pass it on to the processor and chargeback service without storing any data.

Please review the privacy policy of your preferred payment processor for a better understanding of the information they collect, store and use. Because privacy and anonymity are at the heart of what we do, PureVPN has included Coin Payments and Gift Cards in the list of payment methods we accept. These are 100% anonymous payment methods that will protect your privacy.

Consent and age restrictions
----------------------------

We accept the usage of our website, apps, extensions and services by the users as an agreement of our Privacy Policy and Terms of Usage.

The services provided by PureVPN are intended for people 18 years or older. Parents or legal guardians must inform PureVPN immediately about any unauthorized or underage use of our services.

Legal Basis
-----------

Our legal basis for collecting and using your personal information is primarily to provide you our services and may depend on:

* The personal information concerned.
* The specific context in which it is collected.

The only time we collect personal information from users is:

* When the users sign up and enter into a contract with us.
* Where the processing is in our legitimate interests and does not violate your privacy rights.

### Amendments

PureVPN holds the sole right to revise and modify its Privacy Policy whenever deemed necessary to do so. Whenever a revision is made, the updated revision date will be displayed at the top of this page.

PureVPN encourages all users to frequently check this page for any changes to the policy.

Users acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and be aware of any changes. Hence, by using our products, the users confirm that they accept and agree to the PureVPN Privacy Policy and all changes made to it.

Contact Information
-------------------

For any questions or clarity on our Privacy Policy, please send your queries to [legal@purevpn.com](mailto:legal@purevpn.com)

Last updated on 05/21/2022

PRODUCTS

Tools

LEARN MORE

MOST VISITED

ABOUT PUREVPN

HELP

PARTNERS

Connect with us

.png) [](https://app.adjust.com/7owzhrk?campaign=footer_badge_android&adgroup=all_lps&creative=right_aligned&redirect_windows=https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gaditek.purevpnics&hl=en&gl=US&redirect_macos=https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gaditek.purevpnics&hl=en&gl=US&redirect_ios=https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gaditek.purevpnics&hl=en&gl=US)

.png) [](https://app.adjust.com/7owzhrk?campaign=footer_badge_ios&adgroup=all_lps&creative=right_aligned&redirect_windows=https://apps.apple.com/us/app/purevpn-best-vpn-for-iphone/id594506418&redirect_macos=https://apps.apple.com/us/app/purevpn-best-vpn-for-iphone/id594506418&redirect_android=https://apps.apple.com/us/app/purevpn-best-vpn-for-iphone/id594506418)

.png) [](https://app.adjust.com/7owzhrk?campaign=footer_badge_huawei&adgroup=all_lps&creative=right_aligned&redirect_windows=https://www.purevpn.com/applinks/download-app/store/huawei-gallery&redirect_macos=https://www.purevpn.com/applinks/download-app/store/huawei-gallery&redirect_android=https://www.purevpn.com/applinks/download-app/store/huawei-gallery)

© 2007 - 2024 PureVPN All Rights Reserved PureVPN, brand of GZ Systems Limited Intershore Chambers P.O Box 4342, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands

Company Registration No: 2039934

We use 1st and 3rd party cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However, you may visit "Cookie Settings" to provide a controlled consent.

Cookie Settings Accept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.  

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_stripe\_mid | 1 year | This cookie is set by Stripe payment gateway. This cookie is used to enable payment on the website without storing any patment information on a server. |
| \_\_stripe\_sid | 30 minutes | This cookie is set by Stripe payment gateway. This cookie is used to enable payment on the website without storing any patment information on a server. |
| Affiliate ID | 3 months | Affiliate ID cookie |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| Data 1 | 3 months |     |
| Data 2 | 3 months | Data 2 |
| JSESSIONID | session | Used by sites written in JSP. General purpose platform session cookies that are used to maintain users' state across page requests. |
| PHPSESSID | session | This cookie is native to PHP applications. The cookie is used to store and identify a users' unique session ID for the purpose of managing user session on the website. The cookie is a session cookies and is deleted when all the browser windows are closed. |
| woocommerce\_cart\_hash | session | This cookie is set by WooCommerce. The cookie helps WooCommerce determine when cart contents/data changes. |
| XSRF-TOKEN | session | The cookie is set by Wix website building platform on Wix website. The cookie is used for security purposes. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.  

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_lc\_cid | 2 years | This is an essential cookie for the website live chat box to function properly. |
| \_\_lc\_cst | 2 years | This cookie is used for the website live chat box to function properly. |
| \_\_lc2\_cid | 2 years | This cookie is used to enable the website live chat-box function. It is used to reconnect the customer with the last agent with whom the customer had chatted. |
| \_\_lc2\_cst | 2 years | This cookie is necessary to enable the website live chat-box function. It is used to distinguish different users using live chat at different times that is to reconnect the last agent with whom the customer had chatted. |
| \_\_oauth\_redirect\_detector |     | This cookie is used to recognize the visitors using live chat at different times inorder to optimize the chat-box functionality. |
| Affiliate ID | 3 months | Affiliate ID cookie |
| Data 1 | 3 months |     |
| Data 2 | 3 months | Data 2 |
| pll\_language | 1 year | This cookie is set by Polylang plugin for WordPress powered websites. The cookie stores the language code of the last browsed page. |

Performance

 performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.  

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Rakuten Advertising is a third party company that uses cookies on the website, you can view their privacy policy at this address: [https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy/)

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_ga | 2 years | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, campaign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assign a randomly generated number to identify unique visitors. |
| \_ga\_J2RWQBT0P2 | 2 years | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. |
| \_gat\_gtag\_UA\_12584548\_1 | 1 minute | This cookie is set by Google and is used to distinguish users. |
| \_gat\_UA-12584548-1 | 1 minute | This is a pattern type cookie set by Google Analytics, where the pattern element on the name contains the unique identity number of the account or website it relates to. It appears to be a variation of the \_gat cookie which is used to limit the amount of data recorded by Google on high traffic volume websites. |
| \_gcl\_au | 3 months | This cookie is used by Google Analytics to understand user interaction with the website. |
| \_gid | 1 day | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the website is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages visted in an anonymous form. |
| \_hjAbsoluteSessionInProgress | 30 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjFirstSeen | 30 minutes | This is set by Hotjar to identify a new user’s first session. It stores a true/false value, indicating whether this was the first time Hotjar saw this user. It is used by Recording filters to identify new user sessions. |
| \_hjid | 1 year | This cookie is set by Hotjar. This cookie is set when the customer first lands on a page with the Hotjar script. It is used to persist the random user ID, unique to that site on the browser. This ensures that behavior in subsequent visits to the same site will be attributed to the same user ID. |
| \_hjIncludedInPageviewSample | 2 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjIncludedInSessionSample | 2 minutes | No description available. |
| \_hjTLDTest | session | No description available. |
| PAPVisitorId | 1 year | This cookie is set by the Post Affiliate Pro.This cookie is used to store the visitor ID which helps in tracking the affiliate. |

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.  

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_fbp | 3 months | This cookie is set by Facebook to deliver advertisement when they are on Facebook or a digital platform powered by Facebook advertising after visiting this website. |
| fr  | 3 months | The cookie is set by Facebook to show relevant advertisments to the users and measure and improve the advertisements. The cookie also tracks the behavior of the user across the web on sites that have Facebook pixel or Facebook social plugin. |
| IDE | 1 year 24 days | Used by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile. |
| NID | 6 months | This cookie is used to a profile based on user's interest and display personalized ads to the users. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | This cookie is set by doubleclick.net. The purpose of the cookie is to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website. |
| YSC | session | This cookies is set by Youtube and is used to track the views of embedded videos. |

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.  

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_app\_session | 1 month | No description available. |
| \_dc\_gtm\_UA-12584548-1 | 1 minute | No description |
| \_gfpc | session | No description available. |
| 71cfb2288d832330cf35a9f9060f8d69 | session | No description |
| cli\_bypass | 3 months | No description |
| CONSENT | 16 years 6 months 13 days 18 hours | No description |
| gtm-session-start | 2 hours | No description available. |
| isoCode | 1 month | No description available. |
| L-k26wU | 1 day | No description |
| L-KVHA4 | 1 day | No description |
| m   | 2 years | No description available. |
| newVisitorId | 3 months | No description |
| owner\_token | 1 day | No description available. |
| PP-k26wU | 1 hour | No description |
| PP-KVHA4 | 1 hour | No description |
| RL-k26wU | 1 day | No description |
| RL-KVHA4 | 1 day | No description |
| wisepops | 2 years | No description available. |
| wisepops\_session | session | No description available. |
| wisepops\_visits | 2 years | No description available. |
| woocommerce\_items\_in\_cart | session | No description available. |
| wp\_woocommerce\_session\_1b44ba63fbc929b5c862fc58a81dbb22 | 2 days | No description |
| yt-remote-connected-devices | never | No description available. |
| yt-remote-device-id | never | No description available. |

Save & Accept
